Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
Ricky spent his whole life
in service of his country.
They sent him overseas
in the back of a VW Bug
with a thousand fucking costumed clowns
to fight a giant starfish.
We all fucked up, Emilia.
We could have been accountants.
You know who did it?
Killed Ricky?
They won't let me see the files.
You know I can't answer that, sir.
Yeah, I know. I'm sorry.
I understand your desire to know,
believe me.
I'd be the same.
He loved you, you know.
Your son loved a lot of women, General.
Rick. Call me Rick.
Your son loved a lot of women, Rick.
Yeah, but he loved you as a friend,
as well as whatever else.
That is different.
Really.
Yeah.
I hear Waller has it out for you.
Yeah, she put me
on some shit detail in Evergreen.
Project Butterfly, sir.
-Rick.
Well, I hope you know
you'll always be family.
Ricky would've wanted that.
I'll look out for you best I can.
Thanks.
Now, I gotta go mingle with these assholes
that Ricky couldn't fucking stand.
General...
Rick.
The person who did this...
that person, they'll pay.
I'll make sure of it.
Thanks, kid.
Testing, testing.
Yeah.
Everyone have eyes?
Ivory, check.
Maroon, check.
Aquamarine, check.
Fuchsia, check.
Target in sight.
Northwest corner of the park.
Fuchsia, take the shot when you can.
Fucker.
Our boy looks like
he's expecting something.
Fuck.
Hey!
Yo, he just threw away our mic.
Fuchsia. Do you have a shot?
Bitch, get out of my line of sight.
I said "copacetic."
Yeah, I know you did.
It's the warning word, you dumb fuck.
I know.
I need to know the truth about something.
Get the fuck out of here, Chris.
Did it mean anything?
Anything at all,
what happened on the boat?
You were in the clear. Ads saved you,
and then you keep some sort
of dimensional portal bullshit
-in your house. And now this?
-That isn't an answer, Emilia.
Get the fuck out of here.
Did I mean anything at all to you
in that way?
That's all I came here to ask.
Kids are clear. Should we go in?
Not all the way,
but block any path out.
I can't even trust you
to stay away when I warn you.
Your ego is so fucking big,
you somehow think
that you can get out of this,
but you can't.
You can't. You are fucked.
-You are so fucked!
-Why won't you even answer the question?
Did I mean--
No!
No. Okay?
I was drunk. I told you.
I wish it never fucking happened.
And Rick Flag Junior?
Should I take the shot?
-What?
-Was there something between you?
Hold, Fuchsia.
Ivory's already there.
Was I never
even a consideration because...
He was my only friend.
You killed him, Chris.
How could I possibly...
Ivory, go in. Now.
I get it.
Christopher Smith, this is ARGUS!
Put your hands above your head.
Hey, stop!
Fuchsia, take him out.
Fuck!
Come on, Smith.
Put down that adorable little fucker.
You don't need to do this shit.
Need to? I don't need to.
I'm just doing it 'cause I love it.
Take a step closer, Shaft.
Find out how much.
Shaft? You're complimenting me.
That's a novel strategy. Thank you.
-Fuchsia, stand down.
-I can get the shot.
Stand the fuck down.
Another tranq dart could kill Kline.
He's locked into a turning pattern, Flag.
I have a clear shot,
but it's fatal.
Point-zero-zero-two percent
chance of error.
Maroon...
take the shot.
Maroon, hold the shot!
What the--
Target down!
Damn, you got some moves, girl.
You got in my shot.
She's lucky it worked.
Same old Emilia.
Leota speaking.
Why, yes, sir. That is my ad.
He saw my ad!
Yes, sir, that's right.
My many employees and I are very discreet.
Excuse me?
Yes, the silhouette in the ad
is based upon myself, sir.
Right, no.
My head is not square. That is a hat.
I famously wear many styles of hats
as a part of my... mystique
and-- and branding.
Well, yeah, I can wear a hat when we meet,
if that's what you like, sure.
Yes.
What?
Do I do what?
Greek?
Well, yeah.
We actually specialize in Greek at...
Adebayo Security Consultants.
Why, yes. Thank you, sir.
I look forward to meeting you
tomorrow at 8:00 p.m.
Yeah, just text me your address,
and I will see you then.
Okay.
-Bye-bye.
-Bye.
I just got my first gig.
But... when it comes to security,
do you know what "Greek" means?
He asked me if I did Greek.
-When it comes to security?
-Right.
No clue.
But when it comes to prostitution
it means butt-fucking.
-What?
-Yeah.
No offense,
but it sounded like you and that guy
were having a prostitution conversation.
-Sweet baby Jesus.
-Hey.
Don't worry about me.
I never kill prostitutes.
Their lives are hard enough.
Only johns.
I'm not a prostitute, Adrian.
-Okay, sure.
-Geez!
I just heard her having
a prostitution conversation.
Where'd you go, bird?
Where'd you go?
I fucking had him.
Why did you take him down?
The point was
to find the dimensional rift?
You thought we were gonna do
that with Peacemaker dead?
So, you disobey a direct order?
What order?
Staying down while I take my shot.
Nobody told me to stand down, bitch,
and you better back the fuck off!
-I "better"?
-You got complaints, take 'em to HR.
I made a judgment call.
'Sup, John.
I barely know him.
He's acting very familiar.
-There surveillance in here?
-No.
What the fuck did you do?
Did you just poke me?
You set up Peacemaker
to get your job back?
In the text I sent him,
I said "copacetic."
-So?
-That's the warning word.
It means stay the fuck away,
but for some reason, he still showed.
-Why?
-I don't know.
What's the story with this Bordeaux bitch?
-Cyborg.
-Cyborg?
Yeah, part robot.
She was in a plane crash,
all crushed up, and ARGUS replaced
half her body with machinery.
Jesus, okay.
Yeah, I hate her so much.
I used a pre-op photo of her mangled body
as the screensaver on my phone
for a while.
That's fucked up.
Well, I'm not the one who made my brain.
Whatever. She was about to kill Chris,
and the only way I could save
his life was to knock him out.
You knocked Peacemaker unconscious?
To save his life, John.
I couldn't think of anything else.
That's pretty cool, though.
Right now,
I'm afraid Flag's gonna kill him.
Like, literally kill him.
He won't admit it, but all of this,
the surveillance,
everything is about revenge
for Chris having killed Rick Junior.
I know.
So, you gotta put Chris in the books.
-Book him?
-His fingerprints are on file, right?
-I guess.
-You have to book him,
so there's an arrest record.
Otherwise, he's just gonna disappear.
-But they'll know it's me.
-So?
They'll be miffed.
You were just judgmental
about me trying to get my job back.
Yeah, but we exist on completely
different moral spectrums.
I'm famously a gigantic pussy.
For me, just looking somebody
directly in the eyes
is an act of heroism.
Fine.
Go get ‘em, boy.
Go get ‘em!
-Take the cuffs off.
-Sir?
Take off the cuffs and take a walk,
both of you.
Close that shade.
Turn off the recording equipment.
That's a good sign.
-Sir, are you certain?
-Get out, Bordeaux.
Sir, you have every right to be angry.
I admired your son. I liked him.
I just got caught up in a very dark way
of looking at the world.
Fight me, motherfucker!
Fuck you.
That boy was a better man
you could ever dream of being.
Better man I could ever dream of being.
I know, sir.
I know it doesn't give you any comfort.
There's not a day that goes by
that I don't regret--
John, what are you doing?
What?
You booked Christopher Smith?
-Yeah.
-Why the fuck
-would you do that?
-Excuse me
for trying to take some busy work
off everybody's plates.
Now, we have eyes on us.
You moron.
Whoa, you mean, "Thanks, John,
for doing what we're all required
by law to do."
It's good you did that.
What is it, Bordeaux?
Economos booked him.
Yeah, that's it.
That's it.
Good. Good, good, good, good.
Eagly!
God!
We're gonna go get your dad, okay?
We'll be back soon.
Bye, Eagly.
Yeah, baby.
Yeah.
Fuck.
What the hell happened?
I risked my job booking him
which is a common occurrence.
They let him go.
They couldn't risk him
going to the local jail looking like this.
Fucking Flag lit him up.
Yeah, I see.
-Jagger, do you have eyes?
-Yeah.
They're on the move.
I'm tailing.
Be careful.
Will do.
-Sir?
-Perhaps you wanna say
I'm too close to the situation
because Peacemaker killed my son.
I should consider recusing myself.
Well, despite how it may seem,
my priority is protecting
the people of the United States.
I need to find that dimensional rift.
Not only so we can avoid another incident
like the one in Metropolis,
but for a greater purpose,
benefit us all.
I can't say I didn't...
I didn't enjoy pounding on that punk,
but thrills were not my motivation.
But you gave me the order to kill.
Because I knew Emilia...
would stop it.
And now Smith thinks I'm messy
and that I'm motivated by revenge.
Maybe he won't notice
Judomaster on his tail.
Maybe he'll lead us
exactly where we need to go.
Well, sir, I was gonna say,
that asshole killed Rick,
your son and a fellow agent.
And I have no problem
with him being taken out, sir.
But still...
very...
impressive, sir.
Rick.
-It was Harcourt, Ads.
-What?
She fucked me.
How?
I was surrounded by ARGUS agents.
I figured a way out.
I've been in worse fixes, Ads.
Yeah, me too.
-I'm here too. I'm also listening.
-Yeah, I know.
Well, you just said her name twice
and not mine is all.
Even though I'm sitting right here.
I was about to get out.
Harcourt tackles me,
knocks me unconscious.
Chris, there's no way Ems could do that.
Right, she's too petite.
No, she's one of us.
She's an 11th Street Kid.
Well, she fucking did it, all right?
She saw her opportunity to wheedle
her way back into ARGUS, at my expense,
and she took it.
The general would have killed me
in there if it wasn't for Economos.
I don't buy it.
She had to have a reason.
You've gotta talk to her.
We've talked enough.
I'm fucking over it. I'm over all of it.
I'm fucking done.
What do you mean by that?
Nothing.
This is getting a little dour.
Does anyone want to lighten the mood
by quizzing me on some manta ray facts?
Son of a--
Gotcha!
Damn right.
Yeah.
Yes.
Dude.
Don't you think
someone should stay with you?
You don't look so good.
I really just need some privacy, Ads,
all right?
Eagly!
I killed the prime eagle.
Yeah. Yeah.
Come to daddy.
The prime eagle!
Eagly? I didn't mean to--
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Eagly!
He's inside.
Yeah, we got the drones on it too,
Dunkin' Munchkin.
You're not gonna call me that.
Bro, we got a serious situation here.
I don't need your whole PC,
"the proper word for munchkin
is midget" bullshit.
Munchkin means child, not little person,
asshole.
Hey, how am I supposed
to know munchkin science, man?
Let me make myself clear.
You call me Dunkin’ Munchkins again
and I will rip your dick off.
Not metaphorically,
but actually rip your penis
off your body
in a move I learned from a blind monk
in the Himalayas.
Seems like Flag knew what he was doing.
I will get the troops together
and we'll be right there.
Stellar work, Judomaster.
Go fuck yourself.
Okay.
No, no, I knew it yesterday.
I knew.
What is it, Fleury?
We have a location for the Peacemaker.
All right, let's get moving.
I'm gonna pretend you found that.
It's from Chris. Fuck.
What does it say?
Ready for the next adventure, pal?
Yeah.
Fleury, can you hear me?
Fleury, he's going into the rift!
He...
Fuck!
God. He closed the portal behind him.
He can never get back.
Cheeto fingerprints.
-What?
-Judomaster was here.
They must have followed us here.
The location is compromised.
We need to go.
Okay.
Wait.
"I just..."
-Chris, no!
-What does it say?
We have to go.
Call the others on the way.
We need to meet.
There you are. Just in time.
Man, you gotta suit up.
We got a kaiju downtown
tearing shit apart.
What's with the bird?
Rescue eagle.
Name's Eagly.
He's gonna be my sidekick from now on.
Fucking Chrisper. Make it fast.
"Ads, I'm trusting you to tell
the others goodbye for me."
"I know you won't agree
with what I'm doing..."
...but I feel like it's the right thing.
I've tried again and again
to make up for my mistakes.
But I'm not sure redemption
is something that's truly possible.
At least not here.
So... I'm going to make a life
in the other world.
I'm going to be a brother to my brother...
a son to my dad.
And I'm going to tell Emilia, "Yes."
"We'll work on this."
I'll cherish life.
And overcome my trauma
and be the good man there
that I was never able to be here.
Don't be bummed.
I love you all.
Even Harcourt after all that fucked-up,
cunty bullshit she did.
But I don't belong here.
I think that if you and Harcourt
and Economos
turn this alien-dimensional-canister thing
over to ARGUS,
you'll be in their good graces
enough to all get promoted.
Then... everyone will be happy.
Love, Chris. And Eagly.
Adrian okay?
Is it true you knocked out Chris
and turned him in to ARGUS?
No, of course not.
No, he was about to get shot in the head
by a PMSing cyborg,
and the only way I could save his life
was by taking him down.
What?
You're just who I think you are, girl.
And that's a good thing.
You saw Chris use this thing?
I think so.
You just gotta line up the glass teeth
in the right formation in a doorway,
and you pull those switches,
and you got yourself a connection.
Come on.
Where are you going?
Well, we can't use it here.
ARGUS will find it.
Use it? Why are we going to use it?
Because we're gonna get Chris back.
Maybe I can meet another me in there.
Fuck me.
Fuck!
You know, manta ray derives from the Latin
for pancake of the sea.
That's where we get the phrase,
"A manta ray never forgets."
You know, when a manta ray is born,
they come out in the shape of a burrito.
Can we go to Taco Bell?
How many manta rays
does it take for you to shut the fuck up?
-Is it four? Five?
-Let him count.
Is it a murder of manta rays?
Are they even called a murder?
-No, it's a school.
-Someone shoot me in the ass.
What is that? Did you-- No.